Spend Thanksgiving with good ol' Charlie Brown!
A Charlie Brown Thanksgiving is a animation, comedy,
family film directed by Bill Melendez.
Turkey, cranberries, pumpkin pie...
and the Peanuts gang to share them with.
This is going to be the greatest Thanksgiving ever!
The fun begins when Peppermint Patty invites herself and her pals to
Charlie Brown's house for a REALLY big turkey party.
Good grief!
All our hero can cook is cold cereal and maybe toast.
Is Charlie Brown doomed?
Not when Linus, Snoopy and Woodstock chip in to save the (Thanksgiving) Day.
With such good friends, Charlie Brown - and all of us -
have so many reasons to be thankful.
Charlie Brown (voice), played by Todd Barbee.
Lucy van Pelt (voice), played by Robin Kohn.
Linus van Pelt (voice), played by Stephen Shea.
Sally Brown (voice), played by Hilary Momberger-Powers.
Peppermint Patty (voice), played by Christopher DeFaria.
Marcie (voice), played by Jimmy Ahrens.
A Charlie Brown Thanksgiving is a 1973 American television special
based upon the comic strip Peanuts, by Charles M.
The tenth prime-time animated television special in the Peanuts, it originally aired on the
CBS network on November 20, 1973, and won an Emmy Award the following year.
It was the third holiday special after A Charlie Brown Christmas in
1965 and It's the Great Pumpkin, Charlie Brown in 1966.
Except for the opening football gag, it is the first Peanuts TV special to
have a completely original script without relying on the strip.
The film explores themes of holiday, thanksgiving, boy and dog, jellybean.
The tone is lighthearted.